mycreativeshop.com 2015-03-15

# 

Thanks for using MyCreativeShop. This policy explains the what, how, and why of the information we collect when you use MyCreativeShop. It also explains the specific ways we use and disclose that information. We never sell lists or email addresses. 

#### 1\. Definitions

We’ll start with the basics, including a few definitions that should help you understand this agreement. MyCreativeShop (“MyCreativeShop” or the “Service”) is an online template design & customization service offered through the URL www.mycreativeshop.com (we’ll refer to it as the “Website”) that allows you to select, customize, and create your own creative marketing material by utilizing our browser based design software. MyCreativeShop is owned and operated by MyCreativeShop, LLC, a North Dakota limited liability corporation (“MyCreativeShop,” “we,” or “us”). MyCreativeShop has employees, independent contractors, and representatives ("our Team"). As a customer of the Service or a representative of an entity that’s a customer of the Service, you're a “Member” according to this agreement (or “you”). 

#### 2\. Changes

If there are any changes to this Privacy Policy, we’ll post them on the Website on this page. Any changes will be effective as of the date we post on the Website. You may object to any changes within 20 days after they’re posted on our Website, in which case none of the proposed changes will be effective with respect to information that we’ve already collected from you, but will apply only to information we collect in the future. We won't treat information of any open account differently from any other open account. If you object to changes in our Privacy Policy, we’ll have to terminate your account. That said, if we ever changed our Privacy Policy to expand our rights to use or disclose Personal Information for marketing purposes, you‘d be able to opt out without termination. 

#### 3\. Effective Date

This Privacy Policy is effective with respect to any data that we’ve collected, or collect, about and/or from you, according to our Terms of Use.

#### 4\. Questions

If you have any questions or comments, or if you want to update, delete, or change any Personal Information you’ve submitted on the Website, please use our contact form to get in touch. You may also contact us by postal mail at: 

**MyCreativeShop**  
3002 32nd Ave. S, Suite 111  
Fargo, ND 58103  

#### 5\. Information We Collect

Information You Provide to Us: When you register to use the Services, communicate with our customer service team, send us an email, or post on our blog, you’re giving us information that we collect. That information may include your IP address, name, physical address, email address, phone number, credit card information, and other details like gender, occupation, and other demographic information. By giving us this information, you consent to your information being collected, used, disclosed, and stored by us, only as described in our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy. Information from your Use of the Service: We may get information about how and when you use the Services. This information may include your IP address, time, date, browser used, and actions taken by you within the application. Cookies: When you register to use MyCreativeShop, we store "cookies," which are strings of code, on your computer. We use those cookies to collect information about when you visit our Website, when you use the Services, your browser type and version, your operating system, and other similar information. You may turn off cookies that have been placed on your computer by following the instructions on your browser, but if you block our cookies, it may be more difficult (and maybe even impossible) to use the Services. When you play one of the videos on the Websites, the Flash player may use local shared objects, which are also called Flash cookies. We don’t use these Flash cookies for anything, but we can’t stop the player from dropping them (we tried). Web Beacons: When we send emails to registered MyCreativeShop customers, we'll sometimes track who opened the emails and who clicked the links. We do that to measure our Email Campaigns’ performance and to improve our features for specific segments of customers. To do this, we include single pixel gifs, also called web beacons, in emails we send. Web beacons allow us to collect information about when you open the email, your IP address, your browser or email client type, and other similar details. 

#### 6\. Use and Disclosure of Your Personal Information

We may use and disclose your Personal Information only as follows: 1\. To promote use of our Services. For example, if you leave your Personal Information when you visit our Website and don’t sign up for any of the Services, we may send you an email asking whether you want to sign up. And if you use any of our Services, and we think you might benefit from using another Service we offer, we may send you an email telling you about it. 2\. To bill and collect money owed to us. This includes sending you emails, invoices, receipts, notices of delinquency, and alerting you if we need a different credit card number. We use third parties for secure credit card transaction processing, and we send billing information to those third parties to process your orders and credit card payments. To learn more about the steps we take to safeguard that data, see Section 7 below. 3\. To send you System Alert Messages. For example, we may let you know about temporary or permanent changes to our Services, like planned outages, new features, version updates, releases, abuse warnings, and changes to our Privacy Policy. 4\. To enforce compliance with our Terms of Use and applicable law. This may include developing tools and algorithms that help us prevent violations. 5\. To provide customer support. 6\. To protect the rights and safety of our Members and third parties, as well as our own. 7\. To meet legal requirements like complying with court orders and valid subpoenas. 8\. To provide information to representatives and advisors, like attorneys and accountants, to help us comply with legal, accounting, or security requirements. 9\. To prosecute and defend a court, arbitration, or similar proceeding. 10\. To support and improve the Services we offer. 11\. To communicate with you about your account for informational, not promotional, reasons. 12\. To transfer your information in the case of a sale, merger, consolidation, or acquisition. In that event, any acquirer will be subject to our obligations under this Privacy Policy. 13\. To send you informational and promotional content that you may choose (or "opt in") to receive. You can stop receiving our promotional emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in every email. 

#### 7\. Public Information and Third Parties

Blog. We have a public blog on our Websites. Any information you include in a comment on our blog may be read, collected, and used by anyone. If your Personal Information appears on our blogs and you’d like it to be removed, contact u using our contact form. If we’re not able to remove your information, we’ll let you know why. Social Media Widgets. Our Websites include social media features, like the Facebook Like button. These features may collect information about your IP address and which page you’re visiting on our site, and they may set a cookie to make sure the feature functions properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our site. Your interactions with those features are governed by the privacy policies of the companies that provide them. Links to Third-Party Sites. Our Websites may include links to other websites, whose privacy practices may be different from MyCreativeShop’s. If you submit Personal Information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Website you visit. 

#### 8\. Your customized templates

Your creative projects are stored on a server managed by MyCreativeShop but hosted by a third party. We don’t under any circumstances sell or provide any information about your projects to third parties. We aggregate project data to report internally on what templates our members are using the most. This data is used to help direct us on what templates we will produce more of. 

#### 9\. Notice of Breach of Security

Nobody’s safe from hackers. If a security breach causes an unauthorized intrusion into our system that materially affects you then MyCreativeShop will notify you as soon as possible and later report the action we took in response. 

#### 10\. Safeguarding Your Information

To protect your information, our credit card processing vendor uses the latest 128-bit Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology for secure transactions. Our vendor is certified as compliant with card association security initiatives, like the Visa Cardholder Information Security and Compliance (CISP), MasterCard® (SDP), and Discovery Information Security and Compliance (DISC). MyCreativeShop accounts require a username and password to log in. You must keep your username and password secure, and never disclose it to a third party. Account passwords are encrypted, which means we can’t see your passwords. We can’t resend forgotten passwords either. We’ll only reset them. 

#### 11\. Accuracy of Data, Transparency, and Choice

We do our best to keep your data accurate and up to date, to the extent that you provide us with the information we need to do that. If your data changes (like a new email address), then you’re responsible for notifying us of those changes. We only store data about you for as long as it’s reasonably required to fulfill the purposes that gave us the right to access it in the first place. We keep some data indefinitely, including account registration dates and usernames for historical reporting purposes. We’ll give you access to any Personal Information about you that we hold within 30 days of any request for that information you make by contacting us. Unless it’s prohibited by law, we’ll remove any Personal Information about you from our servers at your request. 

#### 12\. Enforcement

We regularly review our compliance with this Privacy Policy. If we receive a written complaint, then we’ll respond to the person who made it. We work to resolve any complaints with our Members directly. Thanks for taking the time to learn about MyCreativeShop’s privacy policy, and thanks for trusting us to handle your creative projects. 

Updated February 18, 2014
